A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Kenya, 1961-1987, 1997; 476; 24 Box(es)
  - Kenya - Social Sciences, 476.S
    - University of Nairobi - Sociology - Teaching Materials - Evaluation, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 217)
    - University of Nairobi - Staff Development, 1969-1973, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 218)
    - University of Nairobi - Staff Development, 1969-1973, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - University of Nairobi - Staff Development, 1969-1973, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - University of Nairobi - Staff Development - Evaluation, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - University of Nairobi - Staff Recruiting Trip, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 222)
- East Africa Region, 1958-1983; 477; 12 Box(es)
  Series 477 contains:
  477 (No program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  477 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture).
  - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administration, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Council, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University of East Africa, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University of East Africa, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - University of East Africa, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - University of East Africa, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - University of East Africa, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - University of East Africa, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - University of East Africa - Allocations and Grant Actions, 1961-1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - University of East Africa - Allocations and Grant Actions, 1961-1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - University of East Africa - Allocations and Grant Actions, 1961-1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - University of East Africa - Evaluation, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University of East Africa - Evaluation - Supplementary Material, 1974, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - University of East Africa - Evaluation - Supplementary Material, 1974, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - University of East Africa - Program Review, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - University of East Africa - Program Review - David Court Report, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - University of East Africa - Supplementary Material, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - East Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 477.D
    - Administration, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Administration, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Administration, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Administration, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture - Supplementary Material, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Makerere College - Agriculture - Supplementary Material, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- Malawi-Nyasaland, 1970-1977; 482; 2 Folder(s)
  Arrangement note
  One subseries as follows:
  482 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards
  - Malawi-Nyasaland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1970-1977; 482.E; 2 Folder(s)
    - Chipeta, Wedson V. C., 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Chipeta, Wedson V. C., 1973-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rhodesia / Zimbabwe, 1959-1988; 483; 2 Box(es)
  Series 483 contains:
  483 (No program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  483 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  483 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards.
  - Bratton, Michael, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bratton, Michael, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bratton, Michael, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bratton, Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Adamchak, Donald J., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Adamchak, Donald J., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Adamchak, Donald J., 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, Feburary 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, March-October 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development, 1988-1989, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Time sensitive material - Open in 2016.
  - University of Zimbabwe - Faculty Development - Supplementary Material, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 0013A)
  - Rhodesia / Zimbabwe - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 483.D
    - Bursell, Einar, 1974-1976, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bursell, Einar - Grant Evaluation, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rhodesia / Zimbabwe - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 483.E
    - Shamuyarira, Nathan M., 1959, 1963-1969, 1972, 1975-1977, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Shamuyarira, Nathan M., 1959, 1963-1969, 1972, 1975-1977, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Uganda, 1959-1986; 492; 8 Box(es)
  Series 492 contains the following:
  492 (No program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  492 A Medical Sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  492 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  492 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards
  492 S Social Sciences.
  - Makerere University, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Makerere University, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Makerere University - Supplemental Material, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Makerere University - Hunter, Susan, February-August 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3A)
  - Makerere University - Hunter, Susan, September 1988-May 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3B)
  - Makerere University - Hunter, Susan, August-December 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3C)
  - Makerere University - Hunter, Susan, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3D)
  - Makerere University - Hunter, Susan, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3E)
  - Ssennyonga, Joseph W., 1983-1984 (Box 001A, Folder 3F)
  - Ssennyonga, Joseph W., 1985-1986 (Box 001A, Folder 3G)
  - Visiting Scholarships and Consultants - Agreements, 1965-1966 (Box 001A, Folder 4)
  - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 492.A
    - Egwang, Thomas G., 1983-1986 (Box 001A, Folder 5)
  - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 492.D
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1959-1968 (Box 001A, Folder 6)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1959-1968 (Box 001A, Folder 7)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1959-1968 (Box 001A, Folder 8)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1959-1968 (Box 001A, Folder 9)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1959-1968 (Box 001A, Folder 10)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - East African Agriculture Organization -Sorghum, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (I), 1970-1975, 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1973-1976, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture (II), 1973-1976, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture - Donation of Equipment, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture - Supplementary Material, 1971, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture - Supplementary Material, 1971, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Makerere University - Agriculture - Supplementary Material, 1971, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Makerere University - Animal Sciences - McIlory, Dean L., 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Makerere University - Soil Science - Flocker, William J., 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Uganda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 492.E
    - Akenda-Ondoga, Valentine J., 1971-1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Akenda-Ondoga, Valentine J., 1971-1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Akenda-Ondoga, Valentine J., 1971-1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Banda, Babwebona Karomba E. J., 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Basiime, David Rulimbe, 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Basiime, David Rulimbe, 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Kabushenga, Hilda M., 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Kakoza, Joseph, 1970-1971, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Kannyo, Edward, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Kannyo, Edward, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Kannyo, Edward - Supplementary Material, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Kariisa, Gabriel M. B., 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Kariisa, Gabriel M. B., 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Katorobo, James, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Katorobo, James, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Kibuka, Robin D., 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Kibuka, Robin D., 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Kiggundu, Suleiman Ibrahim, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Kiggundu, Suleiman Ibrahim, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Kiggundu, Suleiman Ibrahim, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Mugyenyi, Meddi, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Mulira, James, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Mulira, James, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Mulira, James, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Mulira, James, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Obbo, Christine Sally, 1972-1977, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Obbo, Christine Sally, 1972-1977, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Okello-Oculi, Joseph, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Okello-Oculi, Joseph, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Opio-Odongo, Joe M. A., 1971-1978 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Opio-Odongo, Joe M. A., 1971-1978 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Rugumayo, Edison W., 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Sembajwe, Israel, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Tibenderana, Peter K., 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Tibenderana, Peter K., 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Tibenderana, Peter K., 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Tibenderana, Peter K. - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Uganda - Social Sciences, 492.S
    - Makerere University - Agricultural Engineering - Thierstein, Gerald E., 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Makerere University - Economics - Francis, Alfred A. J., 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Makerere University - Political Science Research, 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Makerere University - Social Sciences (I), 1971-1975, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Makerere University - Social Sciences (II), 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Makerere University - Vehicles, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Makerere University - Vehicles - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Sudan, 1972-1982; 494; 1 Box(es)
  Two subseries as follows:
  494 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  494 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards.
  - Sudan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 494.D
    - Agricultural Research Corporation - Wheat Improvement, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sudan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 494.E
    - Abdalla, Abdel Azim Balla, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abdalla, Abdel Azim Balla, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- French West Africa-West Africa, 1971-1982; 495; 3 Box(es)
  495 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  495 S Social Sciences.
  - French West Africa-West Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 495.D
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, February-May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, July 1981-March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, April 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, May-October 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, November-December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Centre for the Exploitation of Trypanotolerant Cattle, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel, 1977-August 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel, August 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel - Supplementary Material, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - West African Association of Agricultural Economists - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - French West Africa-West Africa - Social Sciences, 495.S
    - West African Association of Agricultural Economists, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - West African Rice Development Association (WARDA) - Rice Study, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - West African Rice Development Association (WARDA) - Rice Study, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - West African Rice Development Association (WARDA) - Rice Study - Supplementary Material, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - West African Rice Development Association (WARDA) - Rice Study - Supplementary Material, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Ghana-Gold Coast, 1967-1972, 1979-1982; 496; 1 Box(es)
  496 A Medical Sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  496 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards.
  - Ghana-Gold Coast - Medical Sciences, 496.A
    - University of Ghana - Physiology, 1967-1970, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Ghana - Physiology - Reprints, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ghana-Gold Coast - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 496.E
    - Adansi, P. Mawulom, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2A)
    - Twum-Baah, Kwaki A., 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Twum-Baah, Kwaki A., 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Nigeria, 1959-1992; 497; 31 Box(es)
  Series 497 contains:
  497 (No program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  497 A Medical Sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  497 D Natural Sciences and Agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  497 E Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards
  497 R Humanities and Arts
  497 S Social Sciences
  497 V Virus Studies
  497 W Schistosomiasis.
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administration, 1969, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administration - Housing, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ahmadu Bello University - Housing, 1968-1974, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1973-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1973-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - University College, Ibadan, 1973-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - University College, Ibadan - Agreements, 1965, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - University College, Ibadan - Allocations/Minutes, 1962-1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - University College, Ibadan - Allocations/Minutes, 1962-1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - University College, Ibadan - Program Review, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - University College, Ibadan - Rural Training - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1959-1961, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1959-1961, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1959-1961, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1959-1961, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - University College, Ibadan - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - University of Ibadan - Administration Conference (I), 1975, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - University of Ibadan - Administration Conference (II), 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - University of Ibadan - Administration Service - Rosselot, Max B., 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - University of Ibadan - Administration Service - Rosselot, Max B., 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 55)